Guide to the Afrika Bambaataa hip hop archive, circa 1972-2016.
Bambaataa, Afrika hip hop archive,
- Series IX. Music Collection
  - 12 inch Vinyl
    - Not annotated
      - B
        - Brand New Funk - Brand New Funk '78, 1978; SR-30930; Brand New Funk (Box 147)
          Vibration
        - Brass Construction - Brass Construction 5, 1979; SR-30931; Brass Construction (Box 147)
          Catalog # LT-977; A-side Matrix # LT-977-1
          United Artists Records
        - Brown, Jocelyn - Picking up promises, 1984; SR-30932; Brown, Jocelyn (Box 147)
          Catalog # EZS-7510; A-side Matrix # EZS-7510-A
        - Brown, Yvonne - Goin' down; King of the groove, 1982; SR-30933; Brown, Yvonne (Box 147)
          Catalog # 79903; A-side Matrix # 79903-A G-2
        - Brown, Yvonne - Goin' down; King of the groove, 1982; SR-30934; Brown, Yvonne (Box 147)
          Catalog # MS-601; A-side Matrix # MS-601A